Guide to the Guinevere Turner papers, 1993-1995.
Turner, Guinevere papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Guinevere Turner papers, 1993-1995.
7826
Turner, Guinevere
Circa 0.5 cubic feet.
Newspapers, correspondence, printed materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Publicity, reviews, and fan responses to the movie "Go Fish", and Turner's sketchbook with art for the movie's credits. Includes press packets for its international releases.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Guinevere Turner starred in the 1994 movie "Go Fish" and also was a writer and producer. She was a writer and story editor for the first two seasons of the television series The L Word and appeared in it as the character Gabby Deveaux. Born in Boston, Massachusetts on May 23, 1968, her career has included being the screenwriter of American Psycho and The Notorious Bettie Page and playing the lead role of the dominatrix Tanya Cheex in Preaching to the Perverted. She has also directed several short films, such as The Hummer (2003) and Hung (2005), which have appeared in many international film festivals. In 2014 she appeared in the horror comedy film Crazy Bitches.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Publicity, reviews, and fan responses to the movie "Go Fish", and Turner's sketchbook with art for the movie's credits. Includes press packets for its international releases.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Turner, Guinevere
Subjects:
Gay motion picture actors and actresses -- United States.; Lesbianism in motion pictures -- United States.; Lesbians in popular culture -- United States.; Screenwriters.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Collecting program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Go Fish Promotional Materials, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Eighteenth San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival Ballots for Go Fish, June 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Go Fish Reviews - New York Times, Casting NY, New Orleans Times-Picayune, June-July 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Other - Out Media letter, Boom Boom Room ad, Nightlines New Year's Eve clipping, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- On Our Backs, July/August 1994 (Box 1)
  Contains article "Slippery When Wet: Go Fish and Other Lesbian Fish Films"
- Filmmaker, Spring 1994 (Box 1)
  Contains article "Fish Stories: Holly Willis on Go Fish." Also includes mentions of the film in summaries of various film festivals
- Cineaste, December 1993 (Box 1)
  Contains article "Lesbians Make Movies."
- Eighteenth San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival booklet, June 9-19, 1994 (Box 1)
  Includes brief write-up for Go Fish and a half-page ad for it.
- Eighteenth San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival press book, June 9-19, 1994 (Box 1)
  Includes various press mentions for Go Fish
- Sketch book, October 29, 1993 (Box 1)
  Contains the original drawings for the credits of Go Fish
- Go Fish international poster (Map-case Folder 1)